We've gotten very used to the Internet.
.لقد إعتدنا للغاية علي استخدام الإنترنت
We are constantly sharing information about ourselves and our private lives:
:نشر معلومات باستمرار عن أنفسنا وحياتنا الخاصة
food we eat, people we meet,
،الطعام الذي نأكله، الاشخاص الذين نقابلهم
places we go, and the stuff we read.
.الأماكن التي نذهب إليها، والاشياء التي نقرأ
Let me explain it better.
.دعوني أشرح ما الذي أقصده بشكل مختلف
Right at this moment, if someone attempts to look you up,
،في هذه اللحظة ،إذا حاول شخص ما البحث عنك
they'll see your real identity, precise location, operating system,
،سيعلم هويتك، ومكان إقامتك ونظام التشغيل الذي تستخدمه
all the sites you've visited, the browser you use to surf the web,
،والمواقع التي تزورها .والمتصفح الذي تستخدمه
and so much more information about you and your life
وكثير من البيانات عنك وعن حياتك
which you probably didn't mean to share with unknown strangers,
،التي ربما لم تقصد مشاركتها مع الغرباء
who could easily use this data to exploit you.
.الذين يمكنهم استخدام بياناتك لإستغلالك
But not if you're using Tor!
!ولكن ليس إذا إستخدمت تور
Tor Browser protects our privacy and identity on the Internet.
.متصفح تور يحمي خصوصيتنا وهويتنا علي الإنترنت
Tor secures your connection with three layers of encryption
.يحمي تور إتصالك بالإنترنت بثلاث طبقات من التشفير
and passes it through three voluntarily operated servers around the world,
ثم يمرر إتصالك من خلال ثلاث خوادم ،يديرها متطوعين حول العالم
which enables us to communicate anonymously over the Internet.
.مما يسمح لنا بالتواصل علي الإنترنت بشكل مجهول
Tor also protects our data
تور أيضاً يحمي بياناتنا
against corporate or government targeted and mass surveillance.
ضد مراقبة الشركات والجهات الحكومية .ومراقبة الجمهور
Perhaps you live in a repressive country which tries to control and surveil the Internet.
.ربما تعيش في بلد قمعي يحاول السيطرة علي الإنترنت ومراقبته
Or perhaps you don't want big corporations taking advantage of your personal information.
.أو ربما لا تريد أن تستفيد الشركات الكبري من بياناتك الشخصية
Tor makes all of its users to look the same
تور يجعل كل مستخدم يشبه الآخر
which confuses the observer and makes you anonymous.
.مما يجعل الجهة المراقبة يخطلت عليها الأمر لأنك مجهول
So, the more people use the Tor network, the stronger it gets
،ولذلك كلما زاد عدد مستخدمي تور، كلما أصبح أقوي
as it's easier to hide in a crowd of people who look exactly the same.
.لأن من السهل الإختباء في حشد من الناس يشبهون بعضهم البعض
You can bypass the censorship without being worried about
يمكنك تجاوز الرقابة دون الشعور بالقلق
the censor knowing what you do on the Internet.
.من ان يري الرقيب ماذا تفعله علي الإنترنت
The ads won't follow you everywhere for months,
،لن يتم تتبعك بالإعلانات في كل مكان لشهور
starting when you first clicked on a product.
.منذ اليوم الأول الذي زرت فيه صفحة المنتج
By using Tor, the sites you visit won't even know who you are,
إذا استخدمت تور، لن تتعرف المواقع علي هويتك
from what part of the world you're visiting them,
،والمكان الذي تزورها منه
unless you login and tell them so.
.إلا إذا سجلت دخولك وكشفت عن هويتك
By downloading and using Tor,
،إذا حملت واستخدمت تور
you can protect the people who need anonymity,
يمكنك حماية الاشخاص الذين يحتاجون إخفاء هويتهم
like activists, journalists and bloggers.
.مثل، النشطاء، والصحفيون، والمدونون
Download and use Tor! Or run a relay!
!حمل تور واستخدمه! أو شغل خادم